Manuscript (periodical) Records
Manuscript (periodical) Records
1933-1937
Manuscript (Athens, Ohio)
1.5 linear ft.
Manuscript, a literary periodical edited by Flola Shepard, Mary Lawhead, and John Rood, was published 1934-1936. Collection contains mostly incoming letters, also a few manuscript submissions, a complete run of the periodical, and miscellany. Correspondents include Nelson Algren, Frank Ankenbrand, Benjamin Appel, Ben Belitt, Oswell Blakeston, Warren Bower, John Malcolm Brinnin, Bob Brown, Dee Brown, Jack Conroy, Kyle Crichton, August Derleth, Peter De Vries, Murrell Edmunds, Zona Gale, Harlan Hatcher, Weldon Kees, Sherry Mangan, Alfred Mendes, Henry Miller, Alfred Morang, Irving Wallace, William Carlos Williams, and others.
148790
Biographical History
The literary periodical Manuscript, a bimonthly founded by John Rood (1902- 1974), was first published in January 1934 with John Rood, Mary Lawhead, and Flola L. Shepard as editors. Printed at the Lawhead Press in Athens, Ohio (where the editors also published a pamphlet, Manuscript News), the periodical published eighteen issues. Manuscript took particular interest in the work of new writers and encouraged their submissions without imposing limits on length or format. Among the writers whom it first brought into national print were Irving Shulman, Eudora Welty, and Tennessee Williams. Other authors who appeared in its pages include Erskine Caldwell, Jack Conroy, August Derleth, and James Laughlin. In the mid-1930s John Rood began to devote more time to his sculpture, at which occupation he would spend the rest of his life, and Manuscript ceased publication with the issue of December 1936.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Manuscript Records consist largely of incoming letter files. There are also some submitted manuscripts, a complete run of Manuscript, and miscellaneous items. These records date from 1933, the year before publication began, through 1937, the year after publication ended.
Letter files contain letters sent to Manuscript and its staff (John Rood, Mary Lawhead, and Flola L. Shepard) between 1933 and 1937 are chronologically arranged in boxes 1-3. These are mostly letters from contributors, subscribers, and literary friends of the editors. Besides routine letters regarding subscriptions and di stri buti an, there are covering letters for submitted manuscripts and letters in which the writers discuss submissions, work in progress, and the literary scene of the mid-1930s in the United States. Some other letters are from convicts on the staffs of prison periodicals. Except for an occasional returned letter (so indicated in the Index to correspondence), there are no outgoing letters. A complete name-date index of the letters is appended to this inventory. Among the principal literary figures represented by letters (counts in parentheses) are:
Algren, Nelson (3 letters)
Belitt, Ben (4)
Brinnin, John Malcolm (6)
Brown, Dee (3)
Brown, Robert Carlton ("Bob") (8)
Cerf, Bennett (1 copy)
Conroy, Jack (9)
Cooperman, Hayse (7)
Creekmore, Hubert (1)
DeJong, David Cornel (1)
Derleth, August William (9)
DeVries, Peter (1)
Hatcher, Harlan (4)
Kirkbride, Ronald (3)
Laughlin, James (1)
McKee, Ruth Eleanor (3)
Mangan, Sherry (2)
Miller, Henry (1)
Wallace, Irving (2)
Weidman, Jerome (1)
Williams, William Carlos (1, plus a John Rood letter to WCW)
Other correspondents whose letters appear in number include:
Archbold, Geoffrey
Bower, Warren
Brown, Bruce
Davis, Harry
Decker, Duane
Dingeldey, Elmer W.
Dworetsky (or Dworkin), Bernard
Edmunds, Murrell
Erisman, Robert O.
Harper, Lawrence A.
Horsley, Caperton
Irwin, Theodore
Johns, Richard
Jones, Everett
Kapingen, Rose
Kees, Weldon
Keith, Joseph Joel
Kelm, Karlton
Kelm, William
Kirk, Franklyn
Kraike, Michel
Langford, Gerald
Mamet, Louis
Martin, Curtis
Meeter, George F.
Mendes, Alfred H.
Morang, Alfred
Munson, Fleet
Rivers, Jean
Watts, W. H. J., Jr. ("Jay")
Yezbak, Jacob
These letter files are incomplete. Originally arranged in alphabetical folders, the letters are largely from correspondents whose names fall between A and M. The files for N through Z, including reported letters from Gertrude Stein, Eudora Welty, Thornton Wilder, and Tennessee Williams, are not at Syracuse and are assumed to be lost.
Other files that might be expected in these records, including financial files, editorial memoranda, and galley proofs, are not present. There are no subscription lists, although some lists, apparently of another publication, are enclosed with an undated letter of Duane Decker in Box 3.
Manuscript (complete run) contains a complete set of all eighteen issues of the periodical, January 1934 through December 1936. The collection also contains three Manuscripts submitted to Manuscript, and a small group of Miscellanea.
Arrangement of the Collection
Letter files and the complete run of Manuscript are in chronological order. Submitted manuscripts are alphabetical by author.
Subject and Genre Headings
Literature -- American Fiction; Literature -- American Poetry; Radicalism; Algren, Nelson, 1909-1981.; Ankenbrand, Frank, 1905-1972.; Appel, Benjamin, 1907-1977.; Belitt, Ben, 1911-2003.; Blakeston, Oswell.; Bower, Warren.; Brinnin, John Malcolm, 1916-1998.; Brown, Bob, 1886-1959.; Brown, Dee, 1908-2002.; Conroy, Jack, 1898-1990.; Crichton, Kyle, 1896-1960.; Derleth, August, 1909-1971.; De Vries, Peter, 1910-1993.; Edmunds, Murrell, 1898-1981.; Gale, Zona, 1874-1938.; Hatcher, Harlan, 1898-1998.; Kees, Weldon, 1914-1955.; Lawhead, Mary, ed.; Mangan, Sherry, 1904-; Mendes, Alfred H. (Alfred Hubert), 1897-1991.; Miller, Henry, 1891-1980.; Morang, Alfred, 1901-1958.; Rood, John, 1902-1974, ed.; Shepard, Flola, ed.; Wallace, Irving, 1916-1990.; Williams, William Carlos, 1883-1963.; Manuscript (Athens, Ohio) -- Archives.; American literature -- 20th century.; American poetry -- 20th century.; Periodicals -- Publishing -- United States.; Correspondence.; Manuscripts for publication.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of John Rood, 1967.
Inventory
- Letter files
  - [General], 1933-1934; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - [General], 1934 Jan-Oct; 20 semimonthly folders (Box 1)
  - [General], 1934 Nov-Dec; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - [General], 1935 (Box 2)
  - [General], 1935 Jan-Dec; 12 folders (Box 2)
  - [General], 1936 (Box 2)
  - [General], 1936 Jan-Apr; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - [General], 1936 May-Dec; 8 folders (Box 3)
  - [General], 1937 (Box 3)
  - Undated, by correspondent
    - A-Z, 6 folders (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
  - No year, arranged by month, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Fragments (Box 3)
- Manuscript, label probably in Rood's handwriting
  - Volume 1, Nos. 1-6, Jan-Dec 1934 (Box 3)
  - Volume 2, Nos. 1-6, Feb-Dec 1935 (Box 4)
  - Volume 3, Nos. 1-6, Feb-Dec 1936 (Box 4)
- Manuscripts submitted
  - Crawford, Frances-Elizabeth, Red Letter Day, undated; typescript, 18pp. (Box 4)
  - Hall, Kate Chamberlin, undated; 9 poems, typescript, 9 pp. (Box 4)
  - Le Sueur, Meridel, The Bird, undated; typescript copy, 74 pp. (Box 4)
- Miscellanea
  - Printed material, 1932-1936; undated; 14 items (Box 4)
Index to correspondence
[unidentified] Apr 18, 1935 undated
[—], Carolyn Aug 24, 1936
[A—], Paul Mar 14, 1934
[A—], Paul M. Dec 10, 1934
[D—], Lucille undated undated May 1 [no year]
[R—], G.E. [March 16, 1934] [To Mrs. A.T. Garnhead
Abels, Hilda May 14, 1935 Jun 3, 1935 undated
Aber, Mary Wright Dec 19, 1935
Abercrombie, Gertrude Aug 24, 1935
Abrams, George Aug 8, 1934 undated undated undated undated
Ackerman, Paul E. Jul 22, 1935
Adair, Eileen [Mar, 1934]
Adams, Mrs. W.H. Apr 23, 1934
Agans, Gerald H. Jun 15, 1934
Agcaoili, Teofilo Jun 15, 1935
Ahlgren, Harold Jul 20, 1934 Jul 20, 1936
Alchon, Bernard F. Nov 8, 1935
Alexander, Alice Dec 29, 1933
Algren, Nelson Jan 26 [no year] Feb 25 [no year] Mar 7 [no year]
Allen, Kay Jun 18, 1934
Allen, Walter Randolph Dec.26, 1935
Altshuler, Harry J. Jun 8, 1934 Jul 8, 1934 Jul 14, 1934 undated
Amery, Alfred L. Mar 14, 1934
Anderson, Paul undated undated undated undated
Angelo, Minnie Mar 14, 1934
Ankenbrand, Frank May 11, 1934 May 19, 1934 Aug 4, 1934 undated
Archbold, Geoffry Sep 14, 1935 Oct 1, 1935
Appel, Benjamin [ca. 1934] [Dec 3, 1934] undated undated undated undated undated
Armhurst [K ] H. Oct 3, 1934
Arnold, E.G. Jul 24, 1935 Sep 5, 1935 Mar 30, 1936 May 5, 1936 Aug 12, 1936
Aronson, Max Jun 5, 1934
Ash, Alene Feb 14, 1934 Mar 9, 1934 Mar 14, 1934
Ater, Benjalyn Feb 1, 1936 Feb 12, 1936 undated undated undated undated April [no year]
Atzberger, George E. Feb 13, 1934
Auerbach, William [Sep 27, 1934] Oct 4, 1934
Ayers, Cecil L. Apr 23, 1934
Bakalyer, Florence [Feb 7, 19.34]
Baker, Glenn Apr 23, 1935
Baker, M.E. Mar 13, 1934
Bakjian, Mardie Jay May 28, 1936
Ball, Ernest A. Dec 11, 1933 Mar 1, 1934
Barclay, Elizabeth Ackerman Feb 20, 1934 Mar 30, 1935 Dec 19, 1935
Barnett, James C. Oct 12, 1935
Barrett, T. J. Jan 2, 1934 Jan 5, 1934
Batchelor, G.W. Aug 6, 1934
Bates, Sylvia Hatfield May 27, 1935 Aug 21, 1935 Sep 20, 1935
Beale, Maurice S. Aug 22, 1934
Bean, Doris 0. Mar 2, 1935
Beardsley, James H. Jan 18, 1934
Beardsley, Monroe Sep 8, 1934 Mar 31, 1935
Beck, Eugenie Aug 21, 1934
Becket, Jean C. Feb 23, 1934
Bedford, David Howard undated
Bedford, Virginia Jan 9, 1934
Beiswinger, Charles Apr 14, 1936
Belitt, Ben Feb 14, 1934 Feb 19, 1934 May 1, 1934 Apr 17, 1936
Bell, Beulah Allyne [ca. 1934]
Bell, Lawrence Jan 8 [no year] Jan 15 [no year]
Ben Meyr, Beri [ca. Mar 15, 1935]
Bennett, Dorothy Jan 12, 1934 Jun 29, 1934 Sep 21, 1934 Nov 9, 1934
Benton, Walter Feb 3, 1934
Benz, Margaret Oct 8, 1934
Berger, Eric Nov 1, 1934 Nov 9, 1934
Berkenfeld, Emanuel Jan 9, 1934 Dec 8, 1934 [Apr 21 1936]
Bernstein, David Oct 2, 1934 Dec 12, 1934 Apr 1Q, 1935 Jul 3;:1935
Bernstein, Harry Jan 1, 1934 Jan 16, 1934 Feb 9, 1934 Feb 18, 1934 Sep 14, 1934 Mar 29, 1935
Berry, Catherine E. Mar 20 [no year]
Betchal, Lenore B. Feb 15, 1934
Beyer, Elsie M. Mar 28, 1934
Bezzerides, A. I. [1936?]
Bishop, Marjorie see Craft, Marguerite B.
Blaisdell, Harry L. Jun 7, 1934
Blake, Ellen Nov 11, 1936
Blakeston, Oswell Oct 28, 1935 Feb 17, 1936 Mar 18, 1936 Sep. 12, 1936 [Oct 4, 1936] undated
Blakroyan, Edward undated
Blodgett, Ruth Feb 9 [1934] Mar 14 [no year]
Bodimer, Iris G. Jan 26, 1934
Bogart, William G. May 14, 1934 Apr 17 [no year]
Bolich, C.M. Nov 26, 1934
Bonner, Priscilla Kerley Apr 15, 1936
Bookman, Jerome Dec 4, 1934 Jan 19, 1935
Boshoff, S.L. Jun 10 [no year] Nov 20 [no year]
Bowen, Margaret E. Feb 12, 1934
Bower, Warren Dec 4, 1933 Dec 9, 1933 Jan 12, 1934 Jan 15, 1934 Jan 20, 1934 Feb 19, 1934 Mar 20, 1934 Mar 29, 1934 Apr 12, 1934 [Jun 8, 1934] Sep 14, 1934 Nov 24, 1934 Apr 30 [1935] May 27, 1935 Jul 2, 1935 Mar 26, 1936 Apr 9, 1936 [Apr 25, 1936] May 28 [1936] Jun 5, 1936 Jul 6, 1936 [Aug 7, 1936] Nov 7, 1936 undated Jan 12 [no year] Mar 26 [no year] May 19 [no year] Jul 13 [no year] Jul 27 [no year] Nov 10 [no year] Nov 20 [no year] Dec 20 [no year]
Bowers, Florence W. Jan 28, 1936
Boyd, Headly Mar 19, 1934
Boylston, Mary Louise Jan 16, 1933
Bradford, Charles Oct 22, 1934 Mar 28, 1935 May 24, 1935 Jun 14, 1935 Jul 18, 1935 Jul 26, 1935 Aug 10, 1935 Aug 27, 1935 Sep 4, 1935 Oct 3, 1935 Oct 17, 1935 Oct 30, 1935 Nov 19, 1935 Dec 6, 1935 Jan 29, 1936 Feb 26, 1936 Mar 19, 1936 Aug 3, 1936 Nov 24, 1936 Sep 29 [no year]
Bradford, Kack Jul 29, 1936 undated undated undated undated undated Feb 19 [no year] Jul 31 [no year]
Bradley, Van Allen Jr. [Oct 9, 1934]
Branch, Kabella Jul 20, 1936
Braus, Mortimer Jan 16, 1934 Jan 23 [no year] Feb 21 [no year]
Braverman, Irene Dec 19, 1933
Brentano's Bookstores, Inc. Aug 14, 1936
Bresse, Zona Gale Dec.5, 1933
Bricker, Mary M. Mar 8, 1934
Brinnin, John Malcolm [ca. 1934] Mar 7, 1934 Jun 7, 1934 Feb 5, 1935 Jun 24, 1935 Jul 1, 1935
Brooks, Wilson A. Sep 23, 1934
Brown, Bob (Robert Carlton Brown) Oct 26, 1934 Nov 28, 1934 Dec 13, 1934 Jan 14, 1936 Mar 1 [no year] Apr 8 [no year] Apr 15, [no year] Nov 15 [no year]
Brown, Bruce Dec 28, 1934 May 26, 1935 Jun 28, 1935 Mar 24, 1936 Mar 30, 1936
Brown, Carlton Feb 19, 1936 Mar 2, 1936
Brown, David Elsworth Jan 19, 1934 Feb 5, 1934 Feb 9, 1934 Jul 20, 1934 Jul 25, 1934 Jul 27, 1934 Sep 6, 1934 Dec 7, 1934 Dec 22, 1934 Jan 22, 1935 Feb 27, 1935 May 16, 1935 Jul 13, 1935 Jul 16, 1935 Jul 23, 1935 Aug 16, 1935 Nov 16, 1935 Feb 4, 1936 Feb 26, 1936 Mar 19, 1936 Aug 5, 1936 undated undated undated Dec 30 [no year]
Brown, Dee Aug 8, 1935 May 25, 1936 Dec 7, 1936
Brown, Harry Peter McNab Mar 2, 1935 undated
Brown, Marjorie May 14, 1936 May 26, 1936
Brown, Robert Carlton See Brown, Bob
Brownlow, C.V. May 27, 1936
Bruce, Gale Dec 5, 1933
Brudno, Walter W. [ca. 1934]
Bruen, Michael Mar 16, 1935
Brune, Gunnar Feb 5, 1934
Bruton, Lucile Apr 16, 1935
Buchanon, Madelaine Sharpe Mar 3, 1934
Buck, Ashley Nov 27, 1934 Dec 27, 1934 Feb 7, 1936 Feb 21, 1935 July, 1936 Aug 17, 1936 Nov 22, 1936 undated
Bulin, Ruth S. Dec 26, 1933
Buller, C.H. Aug 23, 1936
Bullock, Vivian May 16, 1934
Burghalter, Joel M. Mar 19, 1935 Mar 22, 1935
Burke, Henry E. Jul 17, 1936 undated
Burns, R.F. Aug 6, 1934
Buscaglia, James [Jan 29, 1934]
Byrne, Josephine Louise Oct 3, 1935
Cade, David W. Dec 29, 1933
Caldwell, Ronald [Sep 11, 1935] Nov 3, 1936 undated
Callahan, Mary R. Mar. 11, 1935
Callow, E.B. Dec 11, 1934 Dec 26, 1934
Campbell, Edward V. Mar 17, 1936
Campbell, J. M. Jun 27, 1936
Campbell, Lillie D. undated
Caper, Dorothy Jul [no year]
Caplan, Beatrice Jun 17, 1935
Cardwell, C.F. Jun 12, 1934
Carleson, Lucille Jun 13, 1935
Carman, G.B. Sep 23, 1935
Carney, Margaret M. Feb 19, 1935
Carosella, Joseph J. Mar 15, 1934 Apr 18, 1934
Carr, Elizabeth Apr. 4, 1934
Carruth, Harry Jr. Mar 22, 1934
Carter, Claude B. Apr 23, 1934 Sep 15, 1934
Carter, Jean Dec 17, 1933
Cary, Douglas V. Jul 10, 1934
Caxton Printers, Ltd. Jul 25, 1935 [Invoices]
Cenderella, Robert Aug 7, 1934 Nov 19, 1934
Cerf, Bennett A. Jan 19, 1934 [To Warren Bower]
Cerri, Nicola Jr. Jul 24, 1935
Chabek, Daniel Mar 3, 1936
Chewning, Lorraine May 15, 1935
Childers, Beulah Jan 19, 1933 Dec 22, 1933 undated undated
Christian, Mary B. undated
Christie, Edward L. May 21, 1934 Jul 20, 1934 Oct 26, 1934
Church, Gertrude N. Feb 17, 1934
Ciezadlo, J.A. Dec 16, 1934
Cisler, Ann Dec 31, 1933
Clark, Earl May 15, 1934
Clark, Emily Mar 11, 1934
Clark, Luella H. Feb 15, 1935
Clarke, E.P. Dec 27, 1933 Jan 6, 1934
Clement, Albert E. Jan 13, 1934 Jun 15, 1934 Jun 19, 1934 Jun 21, 1934 Jun 26, 1934 Jul 8, 1935' Aug 15, 1935 Oct 7, 1935
Clement, Ora A. Apr 5, 1936
Clemons, Helen undated
Clevenger, G. undated Oct 2 [no year]
Click, L.L. undated
Clossen, Anne Marquis Oct 28, 1935
Clough, Thorndike Dec 15, 1934
Clough, Wilson O. Oct 10, 1934
Clugston, W.G. Apr 7, 1936
Coady, Esther Jul 3, 1934
Coates, Grace Stone [Sep 9, 1935] Oct 18, 1935 [Oct 31, 1935]
Cochran, R.W. Jul 22, 1935
Cohen, Abbott S. May 2, 1934 Apr 6, 1935 [Jun 1, 1935] Jan 8 [no year]
Cohen, Morris Feb 23, 1935
Cole, Alice H. Mar 21, 1934 Apr 6, 1934
Collins, Hazel Rawson Dec 4, 1934
Collins, Lenore undated
Conde, D.N. Oct 22, 1934
Conlon, Juda undated
Conner, Aletha Caldwell May 26, 1934 Jul 9, 1934 Jul 27, 1934
Conroy, Jack Apr 10, 1934 [May 12, 1934] [Nov 27, 1934] [Dec 29, 1934] [Jun 27, 1935] Mar 27, 1936 Apr 10, 1936 Jun 1, 1936 [Sep 2, 1936]
Cook, Herbert Aug 28, 1934 Aug 30, 1934 Sep 25, 1934 Oct 15, 1934
Cooney, Marie M. Jan 23, 1935 undated
Coop, Billy Feb 10. [1934]
Cooper, Esther L. Apr 10, 1935
Cooper, Kitty Sep 6, 1934
Cooper, R. McN. May 8, 1934
Cooper, Richard [Aug 19, 1934]
Cooperman, Hayse Aug 6, 1935 Aug 30, 1935 Oct 18, 1935 Nov 27, 1935 Jan 22, 1936 Feb 14, 1936 [ca. May 29, 1936]
Copeland, P. William Apr 8, 1934 Mar 22, 1935 Apr 25, 1935 Sep 7, 1935 Sep 15, 1935 Oct 11, 1935 Feb 22, 1936 Aug 1, 1936 undated 1935
Corcoran, Catherine Aug 14, 1935
Cormack, Margaret Ann Aug 3, 1935
Cosson, Ruth A. [Aug 7, 1934]
Coulter, Alice Nov 18, 1935
Coyle, M. Oct 22, 1934
Craft, Marguerite B. Feb 19, 1935 Jül 2, 1936 undated
Crawford, Frances Elizabeth Jan 8, 1936 Oct 31, 1936
Craytor, Hazel Jan 11, 1934
Creager, Eunice May 6, 1936
Creekmore, Hubert Sep 12, 1934
Crichton, Kyle Mar 29, 1934 Oct 1, 1936
Croman, Rosalind W. Jan 7, 1935
Cronin, James Douglas Jul 30, 1934
Crowley, Arthur W. Jan 3, 1935
Cull, Margaret Dec 28, 1933 Jan 16, 1934 Feb 13, 1934 Mar 3, 1934 Mar 27, 1934 Nov 30, 1934 Jul 4, 1935 undated
Cullen, Hazel Jan 2, 1935 Oct 19, 1935 Oct 24, 1935 Nov 18, 1936 May 12, 1935
Cummings, Dorothy May 22, 1934
Cummings, Thomas Apr 11, 1934 May 11, 1934 Jun 24, 1934 Nov 2o, 1935 Mar 7, 1935
Cunningham, M.J. Oct 29, 1935 Jan 25, 1936
Cunningham, Scott Dec 25, 1934
Curtis, Donald S. Jun 14, 1934
Curtiss, Adelaide Sep 3, 1935
Cutter, 0.E. Feb 13, 1934
DaCosta, Jean Apr 16, 1935 Apr 30, 1935
Daigle, Clarence Sep 18, 1935
Daniels, R. Balfour Nov 28, 1934
Dann, E1ise [ca. 1934]
Darling, Birt Culver Apr 2, 1934 Jan 4, 1935
Darrow, Lincoln Sep 5, 1934
Davidson, D.A. Oct 18, 1934 Oct 18, 1934 Oct 19, 1934 Oct 21, 1934
Davis, Dorothy W. Sep 12, 1935
Davis, Harry (not Harold Lenoir Davis) [Mar 14, 1934] Mar 22, 1934 Apr 4 [1934?] Apr 12 [1934?] May 26, [1934?] Jun 23, 1934 [May 9, 1935] May 27 [1935] Jun 4 [1935] Aug [1935] undated undated undated Jun 10 [no year]
Davis, L. Carl Feb 13, 1934
Davis, Leona Jan 24, 1935
Davis, Ruth Jan 17, 1934
Davis, Z.I. [Feb 13, 1934]
Dawkins, Claude undated Deacon, Richard G. Jun 24, 1934
Deats, William Watrous [ca. 1934] May 28, 1924 [actually 1934] Decker, Duane Jan 15, 1934 Oct 4, 1934 Nov 12, 1934 Feb 15, 1935 Mar 20, 1935 May 25, 1935 Jun 10, 1935 Jul 7, 1935 Sep 29, 1935 [Oct, 1935] Dec 8, 1935 Dec 11, 1935 Apr 7, 1936 May 14, 1936 Jun 14, 1936 Sep 1, 1936 undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated undated
DeJong, David Cornel Feb 26, 1935
DeLacy, Anne Jan 10, 1936 Feb 15, 1936
DeMille, Arnold C. Nov 19, 1934
DeMotte, Fred W. Sep 19 -Dec 5, 1933
DeO11iphant, H.S. undated
Derleth, August W. Jun 9, 1934 Jul 3, 1934 Jul 4, 1934 Jul 16 [1934] Aug 6 [1934] Jan 11 [1935] [Jan 21, 1935] May 14, 1935 Feb 7 [no year]
DeRosi, John E. Jul 26, 1934
Derrickson, Russell Sep 17, 1934
DeSales, Bro. CFX Jan 24, 1934
Desfor, Harold D. Nov 29, 1934 Jan 22, 1935 April 5 [1935?] Nov 6 [no year]
DeVries, Peter [Oct 31, 1934]
DeWitt, Ned P. Dec 1, 1934
Dickerson, Herbert L. Jun 24, 1935
Dickinson, Catherine E. Jul 15, 1936
Dickinson, Tom Mar 8, 1936 Mar 23, 1936
Dillon, Charles E. Dec 1, 1934
Dingeldey, Elmer W. "Ding" Dec 14, 1933 [1934?] Jan 11, 1934 Jan 13, 1934 Jan 18, 1934 Jan 23,. 1934 Feb 21, 1934 Feb 23, 1934 Mar 15, 1934 Mar 29, 1934 Apr 7, 1934 Apr 9, 1934 Apr 29, 1934 May 13, 1934 Jun 6, 1934 Jul 9, 1934 Aug 28, 1934 Sep 25, 1934 Oct 26, 1934 [to Editor, Current Digest] Dec 4, 1934 Jan 6, 1935 Jan 20, 1935 Feb 12, 1935 Feb 17, 1935 Feb 21, 1935 Aug 5, 1935 Nov 13, 1935 Jan 28, 1936 Feb 18, 1936 Apr 26, 1936 May 31, 1936 Nov 9, 1936 Nov 21, 1936 1935 [Frag., to Fleet Munson] Feb 15, 1935 [Frag., to Fleet Munson]
Dionisin, J.C. Feb 2, 1935
Divine, R.J. Feb 17, 1934
D'Nomyer, Viola Feb 12, 1934
Donnall, J. Feb 8, 1935
Doskow, David Apr 6, 1935
Double, Robert Francis Mar 27, 1934 Sep 9, 1934 Jan 27, 1935
Douty, Helen A. Aug 23, 1934 Mar 23, 1936
Dow, Robert B. Jan 11, 1935
Doyle, Pearla Jun 18, 1934
Dragonetti, Mary Apr 15, 1934 Jan 13, 1935
Drews, E.L. Dec 28, 1935
Dreyer, Martin Aug 26, 1936
DuBois, Arthur E. Jun 8, 1934 [Jun 9, 1934] [Sep 8, 1934] [Nov 10, 1934] undated
Ducody, Henry K. Oct 29, 1935
Dukic, Mario C. Dec 11, 1935
Dworetsky [Dworken], Bernard Jan 22, 1934 Feb 25, 1934 Feb 9, 1935 Mar 5, 1935 Mar 7, 1935 Mar 18, 1935 May 9, 1935 May 18, 1935 Jun 6, 1935 Jun 27, 1935 Jul 16, 1935 Aug 27, 1935 Sep 23, 1935 Jan 13, 1936 undated
Dwyer, Ellen Fleming Apr 4, 1936
Dyas, Blanche Dec 13, 1934
Easterling, Narena Mar 30, 1936
Eaton, Guy W. Apr 6, 1934
Ecker, Mary C.W. Jan 27, 1934
Eddy, Eugene J. Jan 8, 1934
Ederheimer, Louise Jul 2 [1934?] Dec 16, 1934 Apr 3, 1934
Edey, Maitland Armstrong Oct 8, 1935
Edgerton, Gladys Mar 20, 1935
Edgerton, Howard H. Aug 29, 1935
Edmunds, Murrell Dec 30, 1933 Jan 5, 1934 Jan 22, 1934 Jan 27, 1934 Feb 5, 1934 Feb 10, 1934 Feb 19, 1934 Feb 20, 1934 Mar 6, 1934 Mar 8, 1934 Mar 12, 1934 Mar 14, 1934 Mar 16, 1934 Mar 17, 1934 Mar 18, 1934 Mar 21, 1934 Mar 26, 1934 Apr 9, 1934 Apr 16, 1934 Apr 24, 1934 Apr 26, 1934 Apr 29, 1934 Aug 10, 1934 Sep 3, 1934 Sep 28, 1934 Oct 11, 1934 Nov 15, 1934 Nov 22, 1934 Nov 23, 1934 Nov 27, 1934 Dec 5, 1934 Dec 12, 1934 Dec 26, 1934 Jan 22, 1935 Feb 1, 1935 Feb 25, 1935 Feb 27, 1935 Mar 14, 1934 Apr 23, 1935 May 6, 1935 Aug 17, 1935 Oct 19, 1935 Jan 21, 1936 Nov 2, 1936 undated undated undated undated
Edmunds-Hemingway, Clara Oct 11, 1934 Aug 6 [no year]
Edwards, Richard Nov 7, 1935 Dec 16, 1935
Elencweig, Sylvan E. Aug 8, 1934
Elliot, William B. Nov 7, 1935
Elliott, Frances undated
Ellis, Francis Royell [Oct, 1934]
Ellison, Hal undated undated [Ellroy?], J. [Jan, 1934]
Elright, Frederick Jul 30, 1935 Aug 23, 1935 Sep 8, 1935
Elroy, Kenneth M. Jul 22, 1935
Elwood, Maren Dec 3, 1934
Elzey, Margaret I. Sep 18, 1934
England, Robert Oct 9, 1934 Oct 30, 1934
Erisman, Robert 0. [1934?] [1934] [Feb 22, 1934] May 13, 1934 May 27, 1934 Jun 5, 1934 Mar 22, 1935 Apr 10, 1935 May 16, 1935 [Jun 5, 1935] Jun 26, 1935 Aug 17, 1935 [Aug 28, 1935] [Dec 5, 1935] Jan 8, 1936 Jan 15, 1936 Feb 22, 1936 [Apr 22, 1936] Sep 28, 1936 undated undated undated undated undated undated
Ervin, Edna Dec 6, 1933
Eshbach, Lloyd Arthur Apr 30, 1935 Jun 20, 1935
Evans, Emerson Mar 14, 1935
Evans, Helen D. Feb 21, 1934
Evans, Mildred Oct 27, 1935
Everson, Lois Mar 21 1934
Fabricant, Noah D. Jul 7, 1934
Faires, Virginia Feb 23, 1935
Faist, M. Dec 18, 1933
Farrell, Edward Jan 17, 1934
Faulhaber, F.V. [May 23, 1934]
Fawcett, John W. Dec 18, 1933 [ca. Jul, 1934]
Faxon, Frederick W. Feb 17, 1934
Fegan, Benjamin Aug 6, 1936 Sep 11, 1936
Feig, Charles [Oct, 1934] Oct 11, 1934
Feldman, Jack [ca. Jan 12, 1935]
Fellows, W.E. Apr 12, 1935
Fenichel, O.M. Apr 24, 1934
Fergusen, James F. Mar 4, 1935 Oct 15, 1935
Ferguson, Torrence Feb 5, 1935 Apr 23, 1935
Ferry, Mrs. Jay R. undated
Field, Benjamin W. Feb 6, 1934 Feb 14, 1934 Feb 28, 1934
"Fine Arts" Dec 5, 1934
Fingar, Floyd S. Apr 28, 1934 "Finis" Nov 11, 1934
Firdusi, [D] Mar 3, 1934
Fish, Ellen undated
Fitch, Morrison Jan 31, 1934
Fitzsimon, Theodore J. [Sep 18, 1935] Nov 15, 1935
Fleck, Grace Mar 18, 1935
Fleischman, Frieda Aug 5, 1934
Fles, Barthold Mar 20, 1934
Flint, E.M. Dec 17, 1933
Flowers, J.M. Jan, 1935
Follett Book Company Feb 20, 1936
Folsom, Florence Dec 18, 1933
Ford, H.S. undated
Foreman, Mary [Jun 14, 1935]
Foster, A.I. Mar 3, 1936
Foster, Cornelia B. Feb 23, 1934
Frank, Joseph undated undated
Frank, Laura Sep 3, 1934 Feb 18, 1935
Franklyn Square Agency [Aug 14, 1936]
Franks, Harry W. Jan 26, 1935
Freedman, Ted Aug 2 [1935] Aug 22, 1935 Nov 7 [1935]
Freeman, Albert Lawrence Aug 6, 1934
Freemont, Esther Feb 1, 1934 undated
Fremont, Gordon Apr 28, 1935 Apr 29, 1935
Frickel, Mrs. Henry B. Apr 4, 1935 Apr 28, 1935
Fried, Jean Apr 28 [no year]
Friedman, Gertrude Mar 26, 1935
Fritsch, Henry E. Jan 4, 1935 Apr 5, 1935
Frye, Archie S. Apr 29, 1935
Fulcher, Paul M. Jan 22, 1935
Fuller, Luella May 25, 1934
Funsten, L.R. Sep 18, 1934 Mar 18, 1935
Furniss, Ruth Pine Mar 12, 1934
Gaffner, J.J. Jul 23, 1934
Gage, G.R. Apr 12, 1934
Gagnon.R.F. Mar 3, 1934
Gale, Lloyd B. Apr, 1935
Gale, Zona See Bresse, Zona Gale
Galligan, Joseph W. [Dec 4, 1934]
Gannett, Gordon H. Apr 1, 1935
Garatt, Maybella Roen May 10, 1934 May 18, 1934
Garber, Stedy Feb 26, 1936 Mar 2, 1936
Gardner, Lela Marshall Jan 24, 1936 Jan 31, 1936 Mar 28, 1936
Garfield, Stanford Feb 3, 1934
Garnett, David May 26, 1934
Garnier, Wilhelma undated